all right I just showed you a video of a
standing exercise that I call the
standing double hip abduction and this
one's the quadrip double hip abduction
but it's transverse abduction so uh
quadrip double hip transverse abduction
so uh again what I like about this is
you get you get hip abduction with both
legs the leg that's on the ground and
the leg that's in the air so you might
know how to do fire hydrants this is
kind of like fire hydrants with a Twist
so from here I'm going to sink down this
way and I kind of position my body this
way so this way
um I load it up into hip adduction
transverse
adduction and then I am going to move
out and come up all the way so I this
leg is going to
transverse abduct while the other leg
does the same so from here sink in get a
stretch in these tissues right here and
then come up all the
way same thing with this
leg so I'm trying to get Max separation
there and it's just a little twist on
those movements to to get more range and
to work both legs at the same time so
give it a
try